<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-02-25T22:39:51+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Soxa</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">An Example Post.</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/02/25/welcome-to-jekyll.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="An Example Post." /><published>2024-02-25T02:01:17+01:00</published><updated>2024-02-25T02:01:17+01:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/02/25/welcome-to-jekyll</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/jekyll/update/2024/02/25/welcome-to-jekyll.html"><![CDATA[<p>Migas polaroid YOLO 8-bit tilde. Sartorial jean shorts chillwave woke hell of. Whatever tousled chambray cardigan mustache, four loko snackwave vape ramps prism woke poke biodiesel. Freegan vegan pinterest lumbersexual tilde, pitchfork fanny pack gochujang paleo raclette cardigan salvia ugh. Locavore tilde keytar gochujang mlkshk. Tattooed quinoa 8-bit chia enamel pin knausgaard organic heirloom scenester meh ugh.</p>

<p>Heirloom disrupt lyft stumptown. Schlitz affogato tattooed leggings, chillwave ramps raw denim pour-over banjo selvage cliche polaroid. Cornhole vinyl echo park +1 health goth. Narwhal hashtag beard, ethical pinterest asymmetrical twee knausgaard squid kale chips irony put a bird on it 8-bit biodiesel cardigan. Occupy normcore gentrify dreamcatcher.</p>

<p>Church-key taiyaki normcore tumblr, kinfolk occupy before they sold out YOLO chartreuse wayfarers scenester coloring book viral actually. XOXO jean shorts hell of shabby chic palo santo. Literally disrupt organic, venmo man braid cronut occupy flannel skateboard fingerstache direct trade. 90’s trust fund edison bulb, enamel pin messenger bag gluten-free literally meditation banjo. Fashion axe pork belly waistcoat, retro quinoa small batch try-hard. La croix retro VHS four loko marfa pitchfork shoreditch cold-pressed hoodie seitan blog. Bespoke yuccie etsy, meh vaporware crucifix austin church-key tousled food truck PBR&amp;B offal copper mug subway tile.</p>

<p>Chia tumblr jean shorts DIY, beard disrupt lyft chicharrones ethical hexagon lomo adaptogen. Bicycle rights XOXO chicharrones blog DIY pinterest taiyaki, dreamcatcher shaman jean shorts disrupt shoreditch cronut. Chillwave butcher whatever af mustache unicorn normcore paleo succulents vexillologist. Gochujang flannel street art vinyl gastropub forage ramps literally shabby chic locavore mlkshk. Offal godard polaroid, bicycle rights heirloom locavore organic sriracha.</p>

<p>Readymade selvage air plant pug distillery keffiyeh master cleanse bicycle rights, church-key tumblr XOXO hell of glossier beard offal. Fam flannel dreamcatcher activated charcoal chillwave, flexitarian leggings stumptown synth actually. Glossier woke franzen, hot chicken ethical taiyaki drinking vinegar yr fingerstache cold-pressed. Tacos single-origin coffee enamel pin wolf jean shorts vaporware austin chicharrones crucifix letterpress stumptown. 90’s taxidermy venmo flexitarian kale chips yr. Lyft church-key af you probably haven’t heard of them tattooed.</p>

<p>Dummy text? More like dummy thicc text, amirite?</p>

<p>You’ll find this post in your <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">_posts</code> directory. Go ahead and edit it and re-build the site to see your changes. You can rebuild the site in many different ways, but the most common way is to run <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">jekyll serve</code>, which launches a web server and auto-regenerates your site when a file is updated.</p>

<p>Jekyll requires blog post files to be named according to the following format:</p>

<p><code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">YEAR-MONTH-DAY-title.MARKUP</code></p>

<p>Where <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">YEAR</code> is a four-digit number, <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">MONTH</code> and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">DAY</code> are both two-digit numbers, and <code class="language-plaintext highlighter-rouge">MARKUP</code> is the file extension representing the format used in the file. After that, include the necessary front matter. Take a look at the source for this post to get an idea about how it works.</p>

<p>Jekyll also offers powerful support for code snippets:</p>

<figure class="highlight"><pre><code class="language-ruby" data-lang="ruby"><span class="k">def</span> <span class="nf">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="p">)</span>
  <span class="nb">puts</span> <span class="s2">"Hi, </span><span class="si">#{</span><span class="nb">name</span><span class="si">}</span><span class="s2">"</span>
<span class="k">end</span>
<span class="n">print_hi</span><span class="p">(</span><span class="s1">'Tom'</span><span class="p">)</span>
<span class="c1">#=&gt; prints 'Hi, Tom' to STDOUT.</span></code></pre></figure>

<p>Check out the <a href="https://jekyllrb.com/docs/home">Jekyll docs</a> for more info on how to get the most out of Jekyll. File all bugs/feature requests at <a href="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll’s GitHub repo</a>. If you have questions, you can ask them on <a href="https://talk.jekyllrb.com/">Jekyll Talk</a>.</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="jekyll" /><category term="update" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Migas polaroid YOLO 8-bit tilde. Sartorial jean shorts chillwave woke hell of. Whatever tousled chambray cardigan mustache, four loko snackwave vape ramps prism woke poke biodiesel. Freegan vegan pinterest lumbersexual tilde, pitchfork fanny pack gochujang paleo raclette cardigan salvia ugh. Locavore tilde keytar gochujang mlkshk. Tattooed quinoa 8-bit chia enamel pin knausgaard organic heirloom scenester meh ugh.]]></summary></entry></feed>